Preliminary Guide to the H. Keith H. Brodie, President, Records, 1963 - 1994 UA.03.61.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1963-1994, bulk 1985-1993
  - Subject Files, 1963-1993 and undated, bulk 1985-1993. Accessions UA95-58, UA95-80, UA95-113, UA95-114, UA96-30, UA96-77, and UA97-65.
    - Computer Assisted Language Instruction, 1985 July-1989 June (Box 36)
    - Computer Science Department, 1985 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 36)
    - Conference of European Rectors: Madrid Meeting, 1986 Oct. 21-1986 Oct. 24 (Box 36)
    - Conference of European Rectors, 1985 July-1987 Sept. (Box 36)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 37)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 37)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1988 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 37)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1987 July 1-1988 Jan. (Box 37)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1986 Jan.-1987 July (Box 37)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 37)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1985 (Box 37)
    - Consortium on Financing Higher Education Misc., undated (Box 37)
    - Continuing Education, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 37)
    - Continuing Education, 1987 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 38)
    - Continuing Education: Judith Ruderman, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 38)
    - Cost Accounting, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 38)
    - Curriculum, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 38)
    - Carnegie Corporation: South Africa (Education & Social Reform I), undated (Box 38)
    - Carnegie Corporation: South Africa (Education & Social Reform II), 1985 July-1987 June (Box 38)
    - Carnegie Corporation: South Africa (Education & Social Reform III), 1985 July-1987 June (Box 38)
    - Dana Foundation, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 38)
    - Day Care, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 38)
    - Day Care, 1987 (Box 38)
    - Duke Childcare Coalition Petition, undated (Box 38)
    - Deane Institute, 1987 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 39)
    - Development: Annual Giving, 1990 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 39)
    - Development: Annual Giving (Susan Ross), 1987 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 39)
    - Development: Annual Giving, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 39)
    - Development: Beatty, Croom, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 39)
    - Development: Calendar, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 39)
    - Development: Calendar, 1986 July-1989 June 30 (Box 39)
    - Development: Duke Annual Fund: Parents Program, undated (Box 39)
    - Development: Foundation Relations: Linda Gerber, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 39)
    - Development: University Gift Records, 1990 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 39)
    - Development: University Gift Records (Dot Brock), 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 40)
    - Development: University Gift Records (Dot Brock), 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 40)
    - Development: University Gift Records, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 40)
    - Development: University: Miscellaneous, 1985-1992 June 30 (Box 40)
    - Development: John Piva, 1985-1992 June 30 (Box 40)
    - Development: Presidents Council, 1988 May-1992 June 30 (Box 40)
    - Development: Prospect/Clearance List, 1986 July-1989 June 30 (Box 40)
    - Distinguished Professors, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 41)
    - Distinguished Professors, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 41)
    - Divinity School, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 41)
    - Divinity School, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 41)
    - Divinity School, Board of Visitors, 1970-1989 June 30 (Box 41)
    - Divinity, Atlanta, GA Emory Divinity Dean & Pres. Conference, Mar. 19-20, undated (Box 41)
    - Dober Associates, 1986 Sept.-1989 June 30 (Box 41)
    - Documentary Studies, Center for, 1988-1991 June 30 (Box 41)
    - Dodson, Paul, 1990 Jan. 1 (Box 41)
    - Dowell, Earl, 1987 Jan.-1991 June 30 (Box 41)
    - Drama Dept., 1992 July 1 (Box 41)
    - Drama Dept., 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 41)
    - Drama Dept., 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 41)
    - Drama, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 41)
    - Drama, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 42)
    - Drama, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment Appropriations, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment Appropriations, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment meeting, 1991 May 31 (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment: Committee on Educational Institutions, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment: Committee on Educational Institutions, 1987 July-1989 June (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment: Committee on Educational Institutions, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment: Misc., 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment: Misc., 1987 July-1989 June (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment: Misc. Correspondence, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment: Nanaline H. Duke Fund, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment: Proposals, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 42)
    - Duke Endowment: Scholarships, undated (Box 43)
    - Duke Press, 1987 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 43)
    - Duke Press: General Correspondence, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 43)
    - Duke University Academic Costume, undated (Box 43)
    - Duke University Flag, undated (Box 43)
    - Duke University Mace, undated (Box 43)
    - Duke University Shield, undated (Box 43)
    - DuPont, 1984 Nov.-1989 June 30 (Box 43)
    - Durham Chamber of Commerce, 1987 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 43)
    - Durham Chamber of Commerce Dinner, Feb. 25, undated (Box 43)
    - Durham Chamber of Commerce, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 43)
    - Durham, City of, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 43)
    - Durham, City of, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 43)
    - Durham, City of, 1986 Feb.-1989 Apr. 30 (Box 43)
    - Durham, City Schools, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 43)
    - Durham, Duke Campaign, 1986-1992 June 30 (Box 44)
    - Durham War on Drugs, 1987 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 44)
    - East-West Trade Center, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 44)
    - Economic Development Committee: Subcommittee on Education & Development, 1990 Jan. 1-1990 Apr. (Box 44)
    - Economic Development, Committees of, 1989 July 1-1990 Aug. (Box 44)
    - Economic Development, Committee II, 1987 Dec.-1989 June (Box 44)
    - Economic Development, Committee I, 1987 Apr.-1987 Jan. (Box 44)
    - Economics Dept., 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 45)
    - Education Program, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 45)
    - Education Program, 1985 Apr.-1989 June 30 (Box 45)
    - Endowment Funds, undated (Box 45)
    - Engineering School, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 45)
    - Engineering School, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 45)
    - Engineering School, 1988 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 45)
    - Engineering School, 1987 July 1-1988 Jan. (Box 46)
    - Engineering School, 1986-1987 (2 folders) (Box 46)
    - Engineering, Board of Visitors, 1983 Nov.-1989 June 30 (Box 46)
    - Engineering School, 1985 June-1985 Dec. (Box 46)
    - Engineering, NSF/ERC Evaluation Sequence, undated (Box 46)
    - Engineering, NSF/ERC Proposal, 1987 Sept.-1989 June 30 (Box 46)
    - English Department, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 46)
    - English Department, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 46)
    - English Department, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 46)
    - Environment, School of, 1990 Sept. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 46)
    - Facilities Planning Department, undated (Box 46)
    - Facilities Planning Management, 1987 May 1-1989 June 30 (Box 47)
    - Faculty Compensation, Committee, undated (Box 47)
    - Faculty Compensation, Committee, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 47)
    - Faculty: Misc. Correspondence, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 47)
    - Faculty: Misc. Correspondence, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 47)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 47)
    - Faculty Salaries Report, 1989 Sept. (Box 47)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 47)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 47)
    - Faculty Tuition Benefits, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 47)
    - Financial Aid General, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 47)
    - Financial Aid General, 1987 July-1989 June 30 (Box 47)
    - Financial Aid Office, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 47)
    - Financial Aid Office, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 48)
    - Food Services, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 48)
    - Food Service Duke University (DUFS), 1985 May-1989 June 30 (Box 48)
    - Ford Foundation, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 48)
    - Ford Foundation, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 48)
    - Forest, The Duke Retirement Project, undated (Box 48)
    - Forest, History Society, 1986 Apr.-1989 June 30 (Box 48)
    - Forestry & Environmental Studies, School of, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 48)
    - Forestry & Environmental Studies, School of, 1987 July-1989 June 30 (Box 48)
    - Forestry & Environmental Studies, School of, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 48)
    - Forestry, Board of Visitors, 1984-1991 June 30 (Box 48)
    - Formula Review, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 48)
    - Founder's Day, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 49)
    - Founder's Day, 1984 Nov.-1989 June 30 (Box 49)
    - Fraternities & Sororities, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 49)
    - Fraternities & Sororities: Students, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 49)
    - Free Speech, undated (Box 49)
    - Fuller, Peyton, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 49)
    - Fuqua School of Business, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 49)
    - Fuqua School of Business, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 49)
    - Fuqua School of Business, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 49)
    - Fuqua School of Business, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 49)
    - Fuqua School Board of Visitors, 1991 Jan. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 49)
    - Fuqua School Board of Visitors, 1989 Aug. 1-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 50)
    - Fuqua Board of Visitors, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 50)
    - Fuqua School, Board of Visitors, 1985-1987 June (Box 50)
    - Fuqua, Board of Visitors, 1986, 1988 (Box 50)
    - Fuqua Residence Hall, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 50)
    - Fuqua, Thomas Center, 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 50)
    - Future of NC Community College, 1989 July 1 (Box 50)
    - Future of NC Community College, 1988 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 50)
    - Future of NC Community College, 1988 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 50)
    - Future of NC Community College, undated (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Futures: Duke, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 50)
    - Gallo, Robert, 1987 Jan.-1988 Feb. (Box 50)
    - Geller, Dr. George B., 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 51)
    - Geller # 2, undated (Box 51)
    - General Telephone Co. of Southeast, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 51)
    - Geology Department, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 51)
    - German/American Relations, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 51)
    - German Languages Department, 1989 July-1992 June 30 (Box 51)
    - Germanic Languages Dept., 1986 Feb.-1989 June 30 (Box 51)
    - Gifts & Grants: Foundations, Misc., 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 51)
    - Gifts & Grants: Foundations, Misc., 1985-1987 (Box 51)
    - Gifts & Grants: Exxon Foundation, 1985 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 51)
    - Gifts & Grants, Individuals, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 52)
    - Gifts & Grants, General Electric, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 52)
    - Gillis, Malcolm, 1992 July 1 (Box 52)
    - Gillis, Malcolm, Arts & Science Budget, undated (Box 52)
    - Gillis, Malcolm: Dean of Faculty of Arts & Sciences, 1990 Sept. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 52)
    - Glaxo, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 52)
    - Government Relations, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 52)
    - Government Relations, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 52)
    - Government Relations, 1987 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 52)
    - Government Relations, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 52)
    - Government Relations: OMB Circular, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 52)
    - Graduate School, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 52)
    - Graduate School, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 53)
    - Graduate School: Misc., 1985 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 53)
    - Graduate School, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 53)
    - Grad/Prof. Student Council of Duke, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 53)
    - Greater Durham Community Foundation, 1986 Mar.-1989 June 30 (Box 53)
    - Griffiths, Phillip, 1990 Jan. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 53)
    - Griffiths, Phillip: Formula Budgets, 1990 Jan. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 53)
    - Griffiths, Dr. Phillip: Provost, 1990 Mar. 1-1991 Oct. 30 (Box 53)
    - Griffiths, Dr. Phillip: Provost, 1989 July 1-1990 Feb. 28 (Box 53)
    - Griffiths, Dr. Phillip: Provost, 1988 July-1989 June 30 (Box 54)
    - Griffiths, Dr. Phillip: Academic Plan, 1987 July-1987 Dec. 31 (Box 54)
    - Griffiths, Dr. Phillip, 1987 July 1-1988 June (Box 54)
    - Griffiths, Dr. Phillip, 1986 Jan.-1987 June (Box 54)
    - Griffiths, Dr. Phillip, 1985 July-1986 Jan. (Box 54)
    - Group for the Advancement of Psychiatry (GAP), undated (Box 54)
    - Hammer, Clay, 1986 Aug.-1989 June 30 (Box 54)
    - Health, Physical Education & Recreation, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 55)
    - History Department, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 55)
    - History Department, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 55)
    - History Department, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 55)
    - History Department, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 55)
    - Homeless Project: Duke, 1988 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 55)
    - Honor Council, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 55)
    - Honor Council, 1984-1988 June 30 (Box 55)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1991 (Box 55)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1990 (Box 55)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1989 (Box 55)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1988 (Box 55)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1987 (Box 55)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1986 (Box 55)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1985 (Box 55)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Honorary Degrees: Committee, 1982-1991 June 30 (Box 56)
    - Honorary Degrees: Folder-Trustee-Faculty Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 56)
    - Honorary Degrees: Folder-Trustee-Faculty Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 56)
    - Honorary Degrees: Folder-Trustee-Faculty Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 56)
    - Housing Concerns, 1989 July 1-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 56)
    - Human Resources: Kahr, Toby, 1985 June-1987 June 30 (Box 56)
    - Human Resources: Misc., 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 56)
    - Inauguration: Brodie, undated (3 folders) (Box 56)
    - Inauguration: file of programs, undated (Box 56)
    - Inauguration: Referrals, 1988 Jan.-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 56)
    - Infrastructure, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 57)
    - Insurance, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 57)
    - Insurance, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 57)
    - Insurance, 1988 Oct. 10-1989 June 10 (Box 57)
    - Insurance, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 57)
    - International Development Research, Center for, 1988 Apr.-1989 June 30 (Box 57)
    - International Development Research, Center for, 1987 July-1988 Mar. (Box 57)
    - International Development Research, Center for, 1986 Mar.-1987 June 30 (Box 57)
    - International Students, 1989 July 1 (Box 58)
    - International Students, 1985 Mar.-1989 June 30 (Box 58)
    - International Studies, 1991 July 1 (Box 58)
    - International Studies, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 58)
    - International Studies, 1986 Mar.-1989 June 30 (Box 58)
    - International Studies: Board of Visitors, 1989 July 1 (Box 58)
    - Investment Office, 1987 July-1989 June 30 (Box 58)
    - Invitations Declined, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 58)
    - Invitations Declined, 1990 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 58)
    - Invitations Declined, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 58)
    - Invitations Declined, 1986 Nov.-1989 June 30 (Box 58)
    - Islamic & Arabian Development Studies, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 59)
    - Jazz Institute, 1986 Oct.-1989 June 30 (Box 59)
    - Job Enhancement Program, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 59)
    - Judaic Studies, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 59)
    - Keck Foundation, undated (Box 59)
    - Keck Foundation, 1987-1989 (Box 59)
    - Langford, Dr. Thomas: Vice Provost for Special Projects, 1991 Mar.-1992 June 30 (Box 59)
    - Law School, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 59)
    - Law School, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 59)
    - Law School, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 59)
    - Law School, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 60)
    - Law School, 1985-1987 (Box 60)
    - Law School Board of Visitors Binder, undated (Box 60)
    - Law School: Board of Visitors, 1984-1989 June 30 (Box 60)
    - Law School: Philippines, undated (Box 60)
    - Leadership Program, 1985 Feb.-1989 June 30 (Box 60)
    - Library: Campbell, Academic Computing, 1989 Oct.-1991 Sept. (Box 60)
    - Library: Misc., 1991 June 30 (Box 60)
    - Library: Misc., 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 60)
    - Library: Misc., 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 60)
    - Library: Misc., 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 61)
    - Lilly Proposal, undated (Box 61)
    - Lord Foundation, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 61)
    - Lord Corporation, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 61)
    - Lord Corporation, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 61)
    - Lord Foundation meeting, 1991 May 29 (Box 61)
    - Luce, Henry, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 61)
    - MS (Multiple Sclerosis) Baker/Butters Roast, 1991 Nov. 7 (Box 61)
    - MacArthur Foundation: Gifts & Grants 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 61)
    - Marine Lab, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 61)
    - Marine Lab, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 61)
    - Marine Lab, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 61)
    - Material Support, 1984-1991 June 30 (Box 61)
    - Mathematics, Center for Computation in Medicine, 1987-1991 June 30 (Box 61)
    - Mathematics Dept., 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 61)
    - Mathematics Dept., 1985 July-1991 June 30 (Box 61)
    - McDonald, Eugene, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 62)
    - McDonald, Eugene, 1986 Dec.-1987 June 30 (Box 62)
    - McDonald, Eugene: Senior Vice President, 1985 June-1986 Dec. (Box 62)
    - Medical Center, Basic Sciences, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 62)
    - Medical Center, Basic Science: Misc., 1986 Apr.-1989 June 30 (Box 62)
    - Medical Center, Basic Science Reorganization # 1, 1987 July 1-1987 Dec. 31 (Box 62)
    - Medical Center, Basic Science Reorganization, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 62)
    - Medical Center, Center for Health Policy, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 62)
    - Medical Center: Center for Living, undated (Box 62)
    - Medical Center, Comprehensive Cancer Center, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 62)
    - Medical Center, Comprehensive Cancer Center, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 62)
    - Medical Center, Duke Hospital, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 62)
    - Medical Center, Duke Hospital, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 63)
    - Medical Center, Eye Center, 1987-1991 June 30 (Box 63)
    - Medical Center, Health Administration Program, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 63)
    - Medical Center, Heart Center, 1987-1991 June 30 (Box 63)
    - Medical Center, Howard Hughes Medical Center Institute, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 63)
    - Medical Center, Misc., 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 63)
    - Medical Center, Misc., 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 63)
    - Medical Center, Misc. #2, 1989 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 63)
    - Medical Center, Misc., 1987 July 1-1989 Dec. 31 (Box 63)
    - Medical Center, Misc., 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 63)
    - Medical Center, Misc., 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 64)
    - Medical Center, Nursing, 1986 Sept.-1989 June 30 (Box 64)
    - Medical Center, Private Diagnostic Clinic, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 64)
    - Medical Center, Psychiatry Dept., 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 64)
    - Medical Center, Psychiatry Dept., 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 64)
    - Medical Center, Psychiatry Dept., 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 64)
    - Medical Center, Psychiatry, Neurobiology Proposal, 1985 (Box 64)
    - Medical Center, Snyderman, Ralph, 1992 July 1 (Box 64)
    - Medical Center, Snyderman, Ralph, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 64)
    - Medical Center, Snyderman, Ralph, 1988 July-1989 June 30 (Box 64)
    - Medical Center, Surgery, Dept. of, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 64)
    - Medicine, Dept. of, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 65)
    - Medicine, School of, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 65)
    - Mellon Foundation, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 65)
    - Methodist Church: Board of Higher Education & Ministry, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 65)
    - Methodist Church: Board of Higher Education & Ministry, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 65)
    - Methodist Church: Board of Higher Education & Ministry, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 65)
    - Methodist Church: Board of Higher Education & Ministry, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 65)
    - Methodist Church Conference, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 65)
    - Methodist Church: Miscellaneous, 1987 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 66)
    - Methodist Church: Miscellaneous, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 66)
    - Microstructure, International Center for the Advanced Study, 1984-1991 June 30 (Box 66)
    - Murphy, Evelyn, 1990 Mar. 1-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 66)
    - Music Department, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 66)
    - Music Department, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 66)
    - National Association of Independent Colleges & Universities, 1991 Jan. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 66)
    - National Association of Independent Colleges & Universities, 1986 June-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 66)
    - National Association of Scholars, 1990 Sept. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 66)
    - National Humanities Center, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 66)
    - National Humanities Center, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 66)
    - National Humanities Center, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 66)
    - National Humanities Center, 1987 Mar.-1989 June 30 (Box 67)
    - National Humanities Center, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 67)
    - National Humanities Center, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 67)
    - National Humanities Center, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 67)
    - National Humanities Center, 1989 Sept.-1990 Nov. (Box 67)
    - National Humanities Center, 1988 May 1-1989 June 30 (Box 67)
    - National Humanities Center, 1987 July 1-1988 Apr. 30 (Box 67)
    - National Humanities Center, 1985 Dec.-1987 June (Box 67)
    - Neurosciences, 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 67)
    - Neurosciences, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 67)
    - Nexus, 1989 Oct. 1-1990 June 30 (Box 68)
    - Nexus, 1989 Mar.-1989 June 30 (Box 68)
    - Nexus, 1989 July 1-1989 Sept. 30 (Box 68)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges & Universities, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 68)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges & Universities, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 68)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges & Universities, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 68)
    - North Carolina Biotechnology Center, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 68)
    - North Carolina Biotechnology Center, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 69)
    - North Carolina: Miscellaneous, 1987 July-1991 June 30 (Box 69)
    - North Carolina: Miscellaneous, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 69)
    - North Carolina, University of (UNC-CH), 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 69)
    - North Carolina, University of (UNC-CH), 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 69)
    - Orientation, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 69)
    - Parapsychology Lab, 1963-1968 (Box 69)
    - Pew Memorial Trust, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 69)
    - Pew Memorial Trust, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Pew Memorial Trust, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Pew Memorial Trust, 1986 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Pew Memorial Trust: Gifts & Grants, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Pew Scholars Program, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Pfizer, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Philosophy Department, 1987-1992 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Physical Plant, undated (Box 70)
    - Physics, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Physics Department, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Physics Department, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Policy Sciences, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Policy Sciences, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 70)
    - Policy Science, Institute of, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 71)
    - Policy Science, Institute of, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 71)
    - Policy Sciences, Board of Visitors, 1984 Sept.-1989 June 30 (Box 71)
    - Policy University, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 71)